what a beautiful moment
[Music]
the nation may the world was celebrating
kevin stewart and bob the last few
thousand years were rough no question
but things were finally going their way
kevin had never been more proud
but something was missing ah yes good
show good
show the crown is gone it's gone
they took everything from me my castle
my reputation things look bleak baby i'm
not gonna lie but now at least i have my
[Music]
no
i don't think so
you have no idea who you are messing
with i am the greatest super villain of
all time
oh where are you
[Music]
are you really going to allow that
little penguin to make off with my crown
oh herb
i'm done
for me
oh
bye-bye
and that is how the minions found their
new boss he was cunning he was evil he
was perfect he
was despicable
[Music]